// File: src/data/booth.js
export const booth = [
  {
    id: 1,
    name: "SCG SEMEN",
    code: 2938,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "Pada tahun berapa SCG mulai beroperasi?",
        options: ["1994", "1995", "1996"],
        answer: "1995",
      },
      {
        question: "Apa saja produk dari SCG ?",
        options: ["PCV & Ubin Keramik", "Furniture", "Kain"],
        answer: "PCV & Ubin Keramik",
      },
      {
        question: "Berapa total karyawan SCG di Indonesia?",
        options: ["7200", "7100", "7000"],
        answer: "7200",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    name: "SCG MORTAR",
    code: 2939,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "Pada tahun berapa SCG mulai beroperasi?",
        options: ["1994", "1995", "1996"],
        answer: "1995",
      },
      {
        question: "Apa saja produk dari SCG ?",
        options: ["PCV & Ubin Keramik", "Furniture", "Kain"],
        answer: "PCV & Ubin Keramik",
      },
      {
        question: "Berapa total karyawan SCG di Indonesia?",
        options: ["7200", "7100", "7000"],
        answer: "7200",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    name: "JAYAMIX & PRECAST",
    code: 2940,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "Pada tahun berapa SCG mulai beroperasi?",
        options: ["1994", "1995", "1996"],
        answer: "1995",
      },
      {
        question: "Apa saja produk dari SCG ?",
        options: ["PCV & Ubin Keramik", "Furniture", "Kain"],
        answer: "PCV & Ubin Keramik",
      },
      {
        question: "Berapa total karyawan SCG di Indonesia?",
        options: ["7200", "7100", "7000"],
        answer: "7200",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    name: "SAHABAT SCG",
    code: 2941,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "Pada tahun berapa SCG mulai beroperasi?",
        options: ["1994", "1995", "1996"],
        answer: "1995",
      },
      {
        question: "Apa saja produk dari SCG ?",
        options: ["PCV & Ubin Keramik", "Furniture", "Kain"],
        answer: "PCV & Ubin Keramik",
      },
      {
        question: "Berapa total karyawan SCG di Indonesia?",
        options: ["7200", "7100", "7000"],
        answer: "7200",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    name: "SCG PARTNER",
    code: 2942,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "Pada tahun berapa SCG mulai beroperasi?",
        options: ["1994", "1995", "1996"],
        answer: "1995",
      },
      {
        question: "Apa saja produk dari SCG ?",
        options: ["PCV & Ubin Keramik", "Furniture", "Kain"],
        answer: "PCV & Ubin Keramik",
      },
      {
        question: "Berapa total karyawan SCG di Indonesia?",
        options: ["7200", "7100", "7000"],
        answer: "7200",
      },
    ],
  },
];
